question_data1 = [
    {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},


    {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]

question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
  "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio's character hunts down the killer of his son.",
  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
  "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
  "question": "&quot;Foodfight!&quot; earned less than $80,000 at box office.", "correct_answer": "True",
  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                    "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words,;Bad Motherf*cker; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
                                    "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
  "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
  "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
  "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.", "correct_answer": "False",
  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                   "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
                                   "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
  "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
  "question": "Shaquille O'Neal appeared in the 1997 film &quot;Space Jam&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
